Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory02 Mss.B.B61.inventory02
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents B
  - Baumgarten, F. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 25; 1p
  - Baumhackl (Box 5)
    - To Pribram, A.F., 1926 July 8
      - enc. with Frank, I.K., 1926 Sep. 27
  - Baur, Auguste (Mrs. Georg) (Box 5)
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 16; 4p
  - Baur, F. (Box 5)
    - To Baur, 1912 July 8
  - Baur, Dr. G.? (Box 5)
    - To Boas, 1885 Feb. 14
  - Baur, Georg (Box 5)
    - To Boas, 1890 June 13
    - To Boas, 1891 May 1
    - To Boas, 1891 May 29; 4p
    - To Boas, 1892 June 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1892 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1894 June 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1894 July 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1894 Nov. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 29
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1896 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1896 May 18
    - To Boas, 1896 July 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1896 Sept 3
    - To Boas, 1896 Sept 16
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 22
  - Bayreuth, Historischer Verein für Oberfranken (Box 5)
    see Waldenfels, Freiherr v.
  - Beach, George R. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1911 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1912 July 24
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 17
  - Beacon (Box 5)
    - To Boas, 1906 June 9
  - Beal, G.J. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 July 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 July 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 20; 1p
    - GJB -- from Hayden, P.M., 1933 Nov. 2
    - GJB -- to Hayden, P.M., 1934 Oct. 16; 1p
    - GJB -- to Hayden, P.M., 1935 Jan. 3; 1p
    - GJB -- to Hayden, P.M., 1936 Jan. 9
    - GJB -- to Hayden, P.M., 1936 Feb. 6; 1p
  - Beals, Carleton (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 1; 1p
  - Beals, Ralph L. (Box 5)
    - To Boas, 1942 Jan. 24; 1p
  - Bean,? (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1929 Aug. 31; 2p
  - Bean, R.B. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 1; 1p
  - Beard, Charles A. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 18; 1p
    - CAB -- from Finkelstein, M.I., 1939 Aug. 13
  - Beattie, J.A. (Box 5)
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 18; 1p
  - Beatty, Willard W. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 26; 1p
  - Beaumont, H. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 6; 1p
  - Beaverson, G. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 14; 1p
  - Beck, Carl (Box 5)
    - 1909 Apr. 15
    - From Boas, 1902 Dec. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 14; 2p
    - CB -- from Wettstein, R., enc. with Lieber, Hugo, 1920 Nov. 14
    - CB -- to R. Mayer, 1903 Jan. 1; 2p
  - Beck, Jean B. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 May 7
    - From Boas, 1917 May 17
    - From Boas, 1917 May 23
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 May 29
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 4; 1p
  - Beck, Maximilian (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1938 May 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 June 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 June 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 June 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 July 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1909 May 4
    - To Boas, 1938 June 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 May 20
    - To Boas, 1941 June 3; op
    - To Boas, 1938 July 4
  - Becke, F. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 1p
  - Becker,? (Staatssekretär) (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1923 July 2; 3p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 8
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 6; 1p
  - Becker, Achim (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 20; 1p
  - Becker, Carl H. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1941 Aug. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 25; 2p
  - Becker, Howard (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 30; 1p
    - H.B. -- to Freyer, H., 1934 Mar. 29; 1p
  - Becker, M.L. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 19; 1p
  - Becker, W.J. (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 19; 1p
  - Beckhaut, B.H. (Box 5)
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 24; 1p
  - Beckwith, Martha Warren (Box 5)
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 25
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1917 May 27
    - From Boas, 1918 Sept 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 May 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 13; 1p
      enc. MWB to Parsons, E.C.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 1 & Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Sept. 11
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 8?1914 Aug. 14; 4p
    - To Boas, 1916 July 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 July 30
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 May 19
    - To Boas, 1917 May 30
    - re: Goldenweiser, 1918 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 6; 5p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, Mar. 15 1921 Apr. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 29; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 13; 5p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 10; 4p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sept. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 23; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sept. 27; 1p
    - see FB Open Letter Re: SPain, 1938 Jan.
    - MWB -- from Barrows, A.L., 1931 Apr. 2
    - MWB -- from Deloria, E.C., 1926 Nov. 11
    - MWB -- from Emerson, Mrs. Jos., 1926 May 5
    - MWB -- from Manly, J.M., 1923 Jan. 13; 1p
    - MWB -- from Merriam, J.C., 1924 Nov. 18
    - MWB -- to Parsons, E.C., 1921 Dec. 12; 2p
    - MWB -- to Roberts, H.H., 1921 May 15; 2p
  - Beebe, H.C. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 8; 1p
  - Beebe, Wm. H.H. (Box 6)
    - To Dr. A. Jacobi, 1894 Feb. 28
  - Beecher, W.D. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 4; 2p
  - Beer, E.F. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 7; 4p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 28; 1p
    - Chetebat, Eleanor Beer, 1928 July 25
  - Beeson, Lewis (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 18; 1p
  - Beger, Herman (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 26
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 17
  - Begold [?], C. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1912 June 26
    - To Boas, 1912 July 6
  - Bahaghel, G. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 10; 3p
  - Behar, N. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 25; 1p
  - Behm, E. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1881 Dec. 22; 1p
  - Behmer, Jos. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 26; 1p
  - Behrend, F. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 23; 1p
  - Behrman, M. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 3; 2p
  - Behrmann, Prof. Dr. W. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 25; 1p
  - Behrstock, Julian (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 7; 1p
  - Behnung?, G. (neé Vogele) (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 2; 2p
  - Bein, Esther (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1894 Oct. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1896 May 25
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1899 May 10; 4p
  - Bekker, Paul (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1935? Dec. 31; 1p
  - Belden, H.M. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 20; 4p
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 17; 4p
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 7; 2p
  - Belgium, Ministère de l'instruction publique (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 24; 1p
      see also, Liégeois, C
  - Belime-Coeuroy, J.A. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 8; 1p
  - Belknap, George N. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1937 May 27; 1p
  - Bell, Alexander Graham (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1902 Nov. 8; 3p
    - From Boas, 1903 June 18; 4p
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1903 Sept. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Sept. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1906 May 8
    - From Boas, 1906 June 7
    - From Boas, 1906 July 31
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 18
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1908 May 23
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 18; 1p
      (from W. Mitchell, Sec'y)
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903??; 3p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 14; 1p
      - (from W. Mitchell, Sec'y), 1903 Nov. 27; 1p
      - (from W. Mitchell, Sec'y), 1903 Dec. 12; 1p
      - (from W. Mitchell, Sec'y), 1904 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Sept. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 May 9
  - Bell, John (Box 6)
    - enc. with Baginsky, P., 1934 June 17; 1p
  - Bell, Robert (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 17
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 May 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 June 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 June 25
    - To Boas, 1886 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1886 Mar. 31
    - To Boas, 1886 May 15
    - To Boas, 1886 May 25
    - To Boas, 1886 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1887 May 2
    - To Boas, 1887 May 10
    - To Boas, 1887 May 30
    - To Boas, 1887 May 31
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 28
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1888 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 May 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1888 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 23; 3p
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 7; 3p
    - To Boas, 1889 Apr. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 July 11
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1889 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1890 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1891 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1896 May 23 & Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1908 May 8
    - To Boas, 1908 June 23
  - Beller, L.S. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 24; 1p
    - see Dodd, W.E. Jr., 1938 July 10
  - Bellevue Library (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1902 Sept. 6
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. (Box 6)
    see Fletcher, Harvey
  - Beloit College -- - Logan Museum (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 13; 1p
  - Belou, Pedro (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 5; 1p
  - Belt, Amelia (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 3; 2p
      see Susman, Amelia
  - Benardete, M.J. (Box 6)
    - see FB RE: Spain, 1938 Jan.
  - Benary,? (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 22; 1p
  - Benck, A. (Box 6)
    see also Penck
    - From Boas, 1924 Sept. 4; 1p
  - Bendann, Effie (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 8; 1p
      - enc. with Barnes, H.E., July 8
  - Bender, M.G. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1936 May 12; 1p
  - Bendick, A.J. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 11; 1p
  - Bendix, Reinhard (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 20; 1p
  - Benedek, T.A. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 17; 4p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 10; 1p
  - Benedict, Ruth F. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1925 June 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Aug. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 May 27; 1p
      - also to Bunzel, Reichard, Dixon, Lowie, McGregor, Nelson, 1929 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 July 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 June 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 5; 1p
    - see AN on Heye Foundation, 1930 July 29
    - To Boas, 1923 Sept. 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1925 June 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1925 June 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 July 18; 5p
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sept. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 8; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 12; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 6; 3p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec.?; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 6 & July 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec.?; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 1
    - To Boas, 1932 July 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 29; 4p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 24; 2p
    - see FB open letter RE: Spain, 1938 Jan.
    - see Urey, H.C., 1938 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1938 July 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sept. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 July 2; 1p
    - RFB -- from Aginsky, B.W., 1936 June 2
    - RFB -- from Boas, E.P., 1943 Feb. 3
    - RFB -- from Butler, N.M., 1940 Oct. 8
    - RFB -- from Champion, M., 1935 July 3
    - RFB -- from Coss, J.J., 1932 Oct. 6
    - RFB -- from MacInnes, T.R., 1938 Aug. 11
    - RFB -- from MacKay, D.M., 1938 Aug. 26
    - RFB -- from Metraux, A., Jr., 1939 June 30
    - RFB -- from Meek, Lois H., 1936 Sept. 24
    - RFB -- from Protat, Ch., 1927 May 30 and July 15
    - RFB -- from Wallersein Co., 1938 June 17
    - RFB -- to Berliner Gesellschaft für Anthrop., Ethnol u. Urgeschichte, 1939 June 8
    - RFB -- to MacKay, DM, 1938 Aug. 19; 1p
    - RFB -- to Ramaswamy, S.V., 1932 July 14; 1p
    - RFB -- to Weltfisch, G., 1929 June 11; 2p
  - Benet, Sarah (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 21; 2p
  - Benet, W.R. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 19; 1p
  - Benignus, Siegfried (Box 6)
    [not in file]
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 June 13
  - Benityez?. A. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 2
  - Benjamin, E.B. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1934 July 12; 2p
  - Benjamin, M. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1902 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 4; 1p
  - Benken, Ralph (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 22; 1p
  - Bennéchem, Edward (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 12; 1p
  - Benner, Thomas E. (Box 6)
    - see FB open letter re: SPain, 1938 Jan.
  - Bennett,? (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 27
  - Bennett, Charles E. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 25; 1p
  - Bennett, H.R. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 13
  - Bennet, Wm. S. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, E.P., 1942 Dec. 22; 1p
  - Benninghofen, P. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 20; 1p
  - Bensaude, M. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 1; 1p
  - Benson, E. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 16; 1p
  - Bente, E.K. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 22; 1p
  - Bentley, Florence Lewis (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 16; 1p
  - Bentley, M. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 9; 1p
  - Benton, F.Y. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1930 July 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 July 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 24; 1p
  - Benziger Bros. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 15; 1p
  - Berdahl, Clarence A. (Box 6)
    - see FB open letter re: Spain, 1938 Jan.
  - Berg, A.A. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, E.P., 1942 Dec. 22; 2p
  - Berg, Gertrude (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p
  - Bergamin, José (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 30?; 5p
  - Bergel, Lienhard (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 7; 1p
    - LB -- to Miss Nichtenhauser, 1936 Mar. 2; 2p
  - Bergen, Fanny D. (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 23; 2p
    - Berger, C.L. & sons, 1920 Dec. 31
  - Bergh, Arthur (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 21; 1p
  - Bergman, S. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 2; 1p
  - J. Bergmann and Co. (J. Bergmann) (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Sept 19; 1p
  - Bergson, H. (Box 6)
    - see League of Nations, 1922 Nov. 4
  - Bergson, L. (Box 6)
    - see McCrea, R.C., 1939 Apr. 22
  - Bergson, M.H. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 8; 2p
  - Berkenau, Paul (Box 6)
    - see Laehr, 1927 Oct. 6
  - Berkenau, Dr. (Box 6)
    - see Schittenheim, A., 1921 Feb. 15
  - Berkey, Charles P. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p
    - CPB -- from Renner, G.T., 1927 Mar. 21
  - Berkson, J. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p
  - Berlin, Bibliothek der Kgl. Technichen Hochschule zu (Box 6)
    see Simon
  - Berlin, Gesellschaft für Erdkunde zu (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p
  - Berlin, H. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1909 May 6
    - From Boas, 1909 July 2
    - From Boas, 1909 Aug. 29
  - Berlin, Post Office (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 19
  - Berlin, Preussische Akademie der Wissenschaften (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 1p
  - Berlin, Univ. Natr.-u. Nervenklinik (Box 6)
    - From Bonhoeffer, 1931 Nov. 30
  - Berlin, Verlagsbuchhandlung Gebrüder Borntraeger (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 2; 1p
  - Berliner, Arnold (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 27; 1p
  - Berliner Gesellschaft für Anthrop. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - To Boas from Benedict, R.F., 1939 June 8
    - To Boas from Benedict, R.F., 1932 Jan 28; 3p
  - Berliner Tageblatt (Box 6)
    - FB -- from Levysohn, Dr. Arthur, 1886 Apr. 4; 1p
    - FB -- from Moose, R., 1886 June 15
    - FB's father -- from Levysohn, Dr. Arthur, 1884 Sept. 17; 4p
  - Berman, Lionel (Box 6)
    - To Boas, 1937 June 15; 1p
  - Berman, Nathan (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 6; 2p
  - Berman, J.H. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 9; 1p
  - Bernard, J.T. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 June 11; 1p
  - Bernays, Edward L. (Box 6)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 15; 1p